Henry Wang

(815) 757-5397 • henry.t.wang@gmail.com • github.com/henrytwang • henrywang.me

Overview

I am a full-stack web developer with a bent on growth.

My passion is building products that people connect with on a daily basis.

My goal is to focus on both conversion rates and the user experience.

Specialties

Ruby on Rails, Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL

Experience

Dev Bootcamp

Apprentice 2013

• 10-week web development apprenticeship. Full stack web development.

Thinkful 2012-2013

Consultant

• I remotely implemented the site redesign and several lead gen landing pages.

Sales4Startups 2012—2013

Mentor & Speaker

• I joined a team of passionate technology entrepreneurs who love to share their insights around the topic of sales. We conducted evening sales seminars and training for startup companies.

Fileboard 2011-2013

Director of Marketing

• I developed Fileboard's product messaging, value propositions, product overviews, white paper, newsletter and marketing strategy. I also conducted demonstrations, webinars, and pricing analysis.

Ace Metrix 2011

Analyst

• I was responsible for operations including data management, analytics, content review, and survey deployment.

AOL 2006-2008

Social Media Consultant

• I landed my first gig ever in high school. User growth and content for Netscape.com portal relaunch. I generated content and helped admin the 500,000+ user community.

Education

University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign B.A. in Communication; Concentration GPA 3.5/4.0

2007-2011